Welcome, you do not know how glad I am that you are all here today.
I am Cero, member of Organization ADN.
For a long time in the Organization we have been investigating what it is that makes some human groups
able to go further than the rest.
Why are there teams that together can achieve feats that seem impossible?
Thousands of years ago,
humanity already showed what it can do when many people share a common goal.
Colossal works,
legacies that still amaze us today.
Among them all,
one rises as a symbol of balance,
effort and precision,
the pyramid.
And we have spent years studying patterns,
cross-referencing data and exploring the mysteries of human creativity,
with an ambitious objective,
to understand and recover the extraordinary creative capacity
that flourished in the era of the pyramids.
Today, at last,
we can say that this effort has borne fruit.
We have identified a very small number of groups
that possess truly exceptional potential.
And you,
are among them.
Today we will evaluate your skills as a team
and you will have to overcome a series of trials
to build your own pyramid.
A construction made of coordination,
ingenuity,
and trust.
To overcome these trials,
you will need the ten terminals
distributed around the room
and some pyramid tokens that we will hand out to you.
These tokens will be non-transferable.
To use them,
you must place them on the square mark
on the upper part of the terminals.
A warning:
we do not allow interference here.
Mobile phones and external accessories
are forbidden.
Your only tools
will be what you have in front of you
and your ability to collaborate.
For now,
this is all I can tell you.
Show me you are a capable team.
The test begins now.